momar.com 2018-06-30

# Privacy Policy :: Momar

###  What information do we collect? 

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or mailing address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

###    
What do we use your information for? 

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

• To send periodic emails

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

###    
How do we protect your information? 

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

###    
Do we use cookies? 

We do not use cookies.

###    
Do we disclose any information to outside parties? 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

###    
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance 

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

###    
Your Consent 

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

###    
Changes to our Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

###    
Contacting Us 

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

Momar, Inc.  
1830 Ellsworth Industrial Dr.  
Atlanta, GA 30318  
USA  
sales.support@momar.com
